懒人游戏美食评测
Lazy Game Food Reviews
So over on my main LGR channel, I needed a visual aid of sorts in the form of a sandwich.
那么在我LGR主频道外，我也要做一期三明治节目以飨观众
But not just any sandwich, a very basic sandwich.
但不是什么好的，就是一个很普通的三明治
Like... just the most simple straightforward sandwich you'd think of when you hear the word 'sandwich'.
就是当你听到三明治这个词的时候，你大脑的头一反应
So, I thought what's more basic than a ham and cheese sandwich
那么，我觉得没有什么比火腿奶酪三明治更普通的了
and well, here we go, we're gonna start with the most basic of breads for such a sandwich.
那咱就开始吧！我们先用这种面包来做这种三明治
Arguably, as a just classic Wonder bread
简单来说。就是那种经典的Wonder牌面包
I don't even know if I've ever had this.
我都不知道我还有这玩意:-(
Let's go for one of these...
先来两片
Wow! That's consistent, I'll give it that.
哇，这两片居然一样，不得不说
That's an admirably processed some bread like product.
确实这个面包产品处理得不错:-|
Keeping that simple sandwich theme going, we've got some Miracle Whip mayonnaise,
为保持三明治的普通，我们来用些Miracle Whip牌蛋黄酱
one of a kind tastes of creamy mayo and tangy dressing.
一种相当浓稠的蛋黄酱，带有浓郁香味
Yeah, it's one of a kind all right.
是啊，就是这种熟悉的味道
I've had it at like a friend's grandma's house as a kid
记得我小时候我朋友奶奶家有这个
and that's probably the last time that I consumed it.
那次是我最后一次吃这个了吧
Actually no, I think my grandparents in Virginia had this at one point
实际上不是，我那住在弗吉尼亚的祖父母家里有一个
and like their awesome old seventies kitchen.
挺配他们家有70年历史的厨房:-)
I mean, just smelling it brings back strange memories.
我的意思是，这个味道唤起了某种奇怪的回忆
Not like, you know, 'Holy crap! This tasted amazing!' kind of memories,
这种记忆当然不是“天哪，老天津卫的煎饼果子太耐人了”这种
but kind of nostalgic ones, nonetheless.
而是某种思乡之情，语文课读点诗就知道:-P
They even 'this is grandma's reinvented potato salad'.
这还是“老奶奶的炒面（土豆沙拉）”味道呢
This really is like the grandparents choice for Mayo.
这个非常像是老辈人会选择的蛋黄酱
And the interest of simplicity, I was just gonna go with straight ham and cheese.
当然，基于这个三明治超级普通，我就打算直接放点火腿奶酪了
But it struck me is a bit sad, so I am gonna put layer of lettuce on here.
但这样对我而言就很单报，那我就再放层生菜叶了
Just again, simple generic leaf lettuce.
再说一遍，就一层生菜叶
It's just lettuce, and I am going for presentation here,
就是生叶啦，现在我要展示
believe it or not. so yeah kinda like that.
额，反正就是展示啦
Now, for the all and important -- 'ham' part of this sandwich and
现在，我要展示这个三明治的“火腿”了
if does it get any more basic than lamb defrost, deli shaved, smoked ham, water added.
如果没有比解冻羊肉做的烟熏熟食火腿更普通的话，而且还加了水:-P
It's a ham like... I'll be honest I kind of like this stuff in a weird way.
这就相当于火腿吧......说真的，在某种奇怪的方面，我挺喜欢的这个的:-P
I mean, look at this! It's just like incredibly thinly sliced.
你看看这个，切的比饭馆里的酱牛肉还薄
It has kind of an odd consistency, almost like it's turkey or something,
这东西和火鸡肉有某种奇怪的相似性
but I don't konw, I guess it's ham.
我搞不清，也许就是火腿吧
Seriously, you put this side by side with their turkey or chicken,
说真的，你要把火鸡肉和鸡肉并排放的话
and I can barely tell the difference.
我没有方法分辨它们
But that's okay.
但这没关系
Hopefully this will make sense when you finally see the resulting LGR video.
希望你在看视频时，我刚才说的都能听明白
Okay, let's keep that blast of cheap food nostalgic going with some Kraft singles American cheese.
好的，咱们继续怀旧的普通三明治制作，这是Kraft Singles American 奶酪
It's a cheese product.
这是个奶酪制品
Actually, cheese, apparently, is always made with milk though
当然，真正的奶酪是用牛奶做的
but I don't know what that means
但是我不懂为嘛要写“牛奶”二字
because it honestly has kind of a plasticy consistency.
因为这个明显有种塑料质感
Truthfully though, I love this on grilled cheese and like quick backyard hamburgers.
说真的，要是在后院做个汉堡的话，加这个再烤一下，那是极好的
Putting this on a sandwich like this, though, is a little bit heretical, in my opinion.
在三明治上面放这个嘛，我觉得就有点奇怪了
But I don't know, I'm just like
怎么说呢，就是那种
'Yeah, I remember these being on cheap sandwiches.' How do I want this?
“啊，我想到普通三明治是啥味的了。”我怎么会想吃呢？
This is important.
这个很重要:-)
Yeah, last and last but not least, what good is a cheap ham sandwich purse and
是啊，这个超普通三明治要放的是
cheap yellow mustard. French's classic yellow mustard.
廉价的黄芥末酱，这个French牌黄芥末酱
Yep, it's mustard.
是的，这就是芥末酱
I'm feeling generous.
我放的还挺多
Alright.
<(￣︶￣)>
I might shuffle around the ingredients a little bit to get it looking nice on camera
我得改这个三明治的角度，一会好
for the thing later I'm doing.
拍照，然后上传朋友圈
But I'm not gonna chop in half because I need this intact.
但我不想半截掉下来，因为我还想吃呢
All right.
好的:-)
Actually, you know what I'm going to take this to another room
实际上，我得要把这个带进另一个屋子
because I need a film in there.
因为我要在此拍照
And this is not getting any chips, because... well, I don't need chips for this project.
然后这个就不附带薯片了，因为我觉得这个没必要
Okay, I changed my mind. I do want chips!
好吧，我改变主意了，我需要薯片
We're gonna go with these UTZ original potato chips.
这回就是这个UTZ牌原味薯片
I haven't had these and oh man, I don't even know how long.
我都不知道有多久没吃了
I'm kind of excited for that.
有点小兴奋呢
Smell that bag and it kind of smells like wet cardboard.
闻这个袋子，好像在闻湿纸板
Oh yeah, that's technically a meal, a pickle spears too fancy for this.
好的，这基本上就是一顿饭了。在这放个酸黄瓜太奢侈了:-P
Well, that certainly is a sandwich, let's give it a shot!
好的，这个基本上就是一个三明治了。现在赶紧消灭
Hmm... Honestly, I mostly taste that Miracle Whip. It's just so weirdly sweet and
额，说真的，这个蛋黄酱甜到齁死我了:-(
the cheese, and that bread, and... You know, just everything it kind of coats the
这个奶酪还有面包就更......反正就
roof of your mouth in a not particularly good way.
塞满了你的上牙床，让你觉得难受:-(
it's just kind of like glue that mushes together and to a consistency with a flavor.
这玩意就像是胶水给粘在了一起，味道没有错层
The ham is not distinctly ham flavored. I don't know.
火腿也没有火腿味，我不太明白
I didn't thought that worst, to be honest.
说真的，这比我想的还差:-(
Like if you added a little bit of tomato, and like better
如果这个再加些火柿子，再用些
lettuce, actual ham, real cheese
好生菜，真火腿肉，真奶酪
good bread, and Duke's mayonnaise, they'd be really good.
好面包，还有Duke牌蛋黄酱的话，那这个就相当不错了
Now then, how about these nuts chips?
那这些薯片呢.......
Is that actually potato?
这玩意是薯片吗？
Yeah, I guess so. It's just a ...
就当是吧，这就有点......:-(
Well, there's a distinct lack of potato flavor.
好吧，这个确实少了土豆的香味
It's almost like chewing crunchy air
这就好像嚼着脆皮空气
with salt. Again, oddly comforting kind of addictive.
还有盐的味道。这种奇怪的感觉真上瘾
It's just sustenance and it gets the job done.
还算有营养，能填饱肚子
Well, I hope you're hungry now. Although I doubt it.
好吧，我希望大家馋了......虽然我很怀疑:-\
Yeah, that's all I got.
那咱就这样？
Mmm sort of
Mmm~好歹意思一下:-|
本视频SuperBart翻译，原作者LGR上传于2018年